Finding Aid for the Incoming Correspondence: Heinrich Meyer Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- K
  - Kolenbrander, D. J, 27 October 1949 (Box 3)
  - Kondruck, Nancy. Undated (Box 3)
  - König, Mr. and Mrs, 31 December 1927 (Box 3)
  - Kopf, ?, 20 August 1966 (Box 3)
  - Kopp, Walter, 7 December 1951 (Box 3)
  - Kornmüller, Helga. (11), 21 July 1954 –13 June 1964, undated (Box 3)
  - Kosch, Wilhelm, 17 April 1950 (Box 3)
  - de Kosinsky, Imre. (2), 27 September 1967 –29 July 1968 (Box 3)
  - Kramer, Frederic J. (2), 20 November 1952 –18 November 1965 (Box 3)
  - Krasuer, ?, 11 August 1951 (Box 3)
  - Krause, Friedrich. (2), 10 February 1942 –24 February 1942 (Box 3)
  - Krauss, Werner (6), 20 June 1954 –16 December 1960, undated (Box 3)
  - Krauthammer, Edsel, 1 May 1963 (Box 3)
  - Krebs, Edgar, 17 May 1950 (Box 3)
  - Kretzmann, O. P, 19 December 1958 (Box 3)
  - Kreuder, Ernst. Undated (Box 3)
  - Kreutzer, H. (3), 19 June 1972 –3 January 1973 (Box 3)
  - Kreuzer, ?, 14 November 1955 (Box 3)
  - Krings, H, 2 March 1964 (Box 3)
  - Krispyn, Egbert, 19 November 1971 (Box 3)
  - Kriz, Mrs. Peter [Laura], 9 September 1971 (Box 3)
  - Krock, Arthur. (4), 30 October 1952 –13 March 1964 (Box 3)
  - Krogstad, J. C, 4 November 1943 (Box 3)
  - Kromphold, Joan D, 3 April 1974 (Box 3)
  - Kroner, Ernest F, 1 February 1962 (Box 3)
  - Krüger, Winfried, 14 July (Box 3)
  - Krumplemann, John, 23 January 1954 (Box 3)
  - Kubly, Hans, 15 September 1970 (Box 3)
  - Kühlbor, Brigit. (3), 12 June 1962 –25 April 1964, undated (Box 3)
  - Külhsipen, Helene, 18 August 1936 (Box 3)
  - Kuhn Jr., Ferdinand. (2), 23 June 1941 –8 September 1941 (Box 3)
  - Kuhn, Hans, 10 December 1971 (Box 3)
  - Kuhn, Helmut. (2), 5 April 1934 –23 June 1934 (Box 3)
  - Kunstmann, John G. (2), 13 July 1954 –16 July 1954 (Box 3)
  - Kupferberg Verlag, F, 4 May 1953 (Box 3)
  - Kurath, William, 25 August 1941 (Box 3)
  - Kurrelinger, J, 11 January 1941 (Box 3)
  - Kurth, Liselotte E. (4), 15 May 1967 –14 October 1967, undated (Box 3)
  - Kurtz, John W, 17 February 1964 (Box 3)
- L
  - Lach, Harvey, 22 August 1946 (Box 3)
  - Lagemann, Robert T. (4), 20 November 1963 –10 May 1972 (Box 3)
  - Lajos, Suranyi, 24 February 1939 (Box 3)
  - Lang & Cie., Herbert. [Larry] (8), 13 October 1947 -1971 (Box 3)
  - Lang, Martin, 23 June 1945 (Box 3)
  - Lang, Peter. Undated (Box 3)
  - Lang?, Renee, 14 November 1963 (Box 3)
  - Lange, Victor. (14), 20 May 1942 –18 March 1951, undated (Box 3)
  - Langemaier, Th. (2), 3 June 1951 –2 December 1951 (Box 3)
  - Langer, William. (4), 3 November 1949 –2 July 1952, undated (Box 3)
  - Lanzrath, Sigrid, 3 December 1963 (Box 3)
  - Lasnitzki, Arthur. (2), 20 July 1946 –18 September 1946 (Box 3)
  - Lattmann, Dieter, 11 September 1959 (Box 3)
  - Laubach, Anna, 6 January 1967 (Box 3)
  - Laudenslager, Harriet, 18 April 1960 (Box 3)
  - Lauger, Bill and Lydia. Christmas card, undated (Box 3)
  - Laurie, Alex, 31 October 1945 (Box 3)
  - Lavater-Sloman, Mary. (5), 2 August 1965 –20 November 1966 (Box 3)
  - Lawrence, Oliver [Larry]. (12), 10 April 1946 –24 October 1952, undated (Box 3)
  - Lawrence, Seymour, 16 August 1954 (Box 3)
  - Lear, F. S. (2), 23 January 1949 –2 September 1963 (Box 3)
  - Leblon, Jean, 14 March 1970 (Box 3)
  - Ledermann, Marie G, 7 September 1949 (Box 3)
  - Lee, Sara Jane. Undated (Box 3)
  - Leek, Gilberta. Undated (Box 3)
  - Leeman, O. T, 26 November 1947 (Box 3)
  - Leen, Agnes T, 3 November 1972 (Box 3)
  - Leger, E, 6 October 1942 (Box 3)
  - Leginski, Walter, 6 October 1966 (Box 3)
  - Lehmann, Dorothy, 18 September 1940 (Box 3)
  - Lehmann, Ruth, 9 December 1966 (Box 3)
  - Lehmann, Winfred. P. (9), 14 April 1960 –9 April 1973 (Box 3)
  - Lehner, ? (2), 7 July 1952 –17 July 1953 (Box 3)
  - Leighton, Josephine. (3), 3 April 1953 –9 April 1953 (Box 3)
  - Leisy, Ernest E. (3), 19 December 1945 –24 January 1946 (Box 3)
  - Leithman. Ted. Undated (Box 3)
  - Lembke, Hans. (9), 27 September 1929 –2 May 1948 (Box 3)
  - Lemmon, Larry, 19 April 1947 (Box 3)
  - Lenel, Jane, 1 February 1962 (Box 3)
  - Lentz, W. (2), 29 November 1999 –5 December 1967 (Box 3)
  - Lenzen, Heinrich T, 2 December 1959 (Box 3)
  - Leonard, Barry Alan, 19 January 1961 (Box 3)
  - Leopold, W. F, 9 January 1941 (Box 3)
  - Lepke, A, 4 July 1953 (Box 3)
  - Leppin, Aaron, 20 July 1970 (Box 3)
  - Lepp?, Wolfgang, 23 December 1971 (Box 3)
  - Lessard, Gene J, 8 February 1961 (Box 3)
  - Lessen, Freidrich. (7), 28 July 1943 –28 August 1951 (Box 3)
  - Lester, Richard A. (2), 16 December 1969 –6 January 1970 (Box 3)
  - Leumann, Ernst, 19 December 1927 (Box 3)
  - Leutner, W. G, 3 January 1935 (Box 3)
  - Levin, Harry, 3 February 1956 (Box 3)
  - Lewis Jr., Earl N. Undated (Box 3)
  - Lewis, Wilmarth Sheldon, 28 November 1949 (Box 3)
  - Lewisohn, Ludwig, 17 November 1949 (Box 3)
  - Liebert, Arthur. (29), 29 April 1936 –3 May 1939, undated (Box 3)
  - Liesthe, Norbert R, 19 February 1942 (Box 3)
  - Lieze, Wolfgang, 20 March 1952 (Box 3)
  - Lipkin, Sol. (2), 2 February 1943 –11 December 1958 (Box 3)
  - Lischer, Annelie, 2 July 1965 (Box 3)
  - Little, Ernest L, 20 December 1945 (Box 3)
  - Littman, Edward H. (4), 1 June 1936 –27 March 1951 (Box 3)
  - Littorf? (2), 1973? (Box 3)
  - Locher, Kaspar T. (2), 30 December 1958 –18 May 1970 (Box 3)
  - Lockard, Thaddeus C. (6), 19 March 1964 –4 January 1968 (Box 3)
  - von Lojewski, R, 12 November 1949 (Box 3)
  - Long, Percy W. (6), 26 September 1937 –22 March 1944, undated (Box 3)
  - Loose, Gerhard. (4), 14 September 1938 -3 November 1967 (Box 3)
  - Lord, Russell, 16 February 1946 (Box 3)
  - Lorish, R. E, 17 April 1951 (Box 3)
  - Lory, Jean, 26 December 1963 (Box 3)
  - Louis, Andrew. (2), 26 October 1940 –Christmas 1952 (Box 3)
  - Loyd, Marjorie Lynne. (2) Undated (Box 3)
  - Lubiner, Jacob, 17 September 1947 (Box 3)
  - Lucy, William Davis Cleveland, 1939 (Box 3)
  - Ludos, Eva, 3 January 1961 (Box 3)
  - Luding?, Helen, 17 March 1956 (Box 3)
  - Ludow Jr., George C, 8 December 1950 (Box 3)
  - Ludwig, N. I, 9 November 1947 (Box 3)
  - Lugeon, Jean, 22 November 1948 (Box 3)
  - Lun?, Hans, 16 March 1954 (Box 3)
  - Lundeen, Ruth. (2), 10 April 1948, undated (Box 3)
  - Lunding, Erik. (3), 16 December 1949 –11 November 1966 (Box 3)
  - Luschnat, David. (2), 20 October 1959 –19 December 1959 (Box 3)
  - Lusevke, ?, 26 July 1930 (Box 3)
  - Luten, Carol Ann, 30 December 1953 (Box 3)
  - Luther, Cletis E, 5 July 1967 (Box 3)
  - Lutman, B. F. (11), 29 July 1945 –11 January 1948, undated (Box 3)
  - Lüybex, Dirk. (2), 13 February 1951 –22 February 1951 (Box 3)
  - Lynch, Eleanor, 27 July 1973 (Box 3)
  - Lynch, Juanita. (2), 18 June 1947, undated (Box 3)
  - Lynch, Warren, 18 March 1965 (Box 3)
- M
  - Macaulay, Adrienne, 8 September 1971 (Box 3)
  - MacDonald, J. A. Undated (Box 3)
  - MacGillivray, J. R, 10 February 1954 (Box 3)
  - MacGregor, Howard M, 1 March 1951 (Box 3)
  - Mack, James D, 27 July 1950 (Box 3)
  - Mackenzie, Don. (2), 22 April 1961, undated (Box 3)
  - MacKay, Alastair I. (5), 14 October 1944 –11 November 1948, undated (Box 3)
  - MacMurphey, Robert H, 3 February 1960 (Box 3)
  - MacNaughton, Mr. and Mrs. James. Undated (Box 3)
  - Mady, Cristopher, 18 December 1952 (Box 3)
  - Magill, C. P, 26 February 1953 (Box 3)
  - Magness, J. R, 5 July 1945 (Box 3)
  - Magnus, Uwe, 1 December 1967 (Box 3)
  - Magram, Helen, 30 July 1945 (Box 3)
  - Mahle, Margaret and Hans, 4 May 1948 (Box 3)
  - Maier, H, 16 June 1947 (Box 3)
  - Majonica, Ernst, 4 December 1954 (Box 3)
  - Male Jr., Roy R, 12 January 1956 (Box 3)
  - Malfiat?, Kurt, 29 August 1949 (Box 3)
  - Mall, G. (2), 29 May 1969 –16 December 1969 (Box 3)
  - Mallard, K. S. Undated (Box 3)
  - Mallenauer, Robert, 12 January 1967 (Box 3)
  - Malone, Kemp. (2), 12 January 1963 –10 February 1967 (Box 3)
  - Manchester, Alan K, 26 March 1955 (Box 3)
  - Mandeville, C. E. (3), 20 September 1949 –22 October 1949, undated (Box 3)
  - Manfredi, L. F. (2), 26 August 1947 –23 April 1948 (Box 3)
  - March, John. (2), 2 October 1954 –11 October 1954 (Box 3)
  - Margulies, Adela. (3) Undated (Box 3)
  - Marks, Harry, 10 May 1936 (Box 3)
  - Marsch, Edgar. (2), 1 July 1972 –15 September 1972 (Box 3)
  - Marsh, T. N. (5), 15 October 1962 –30 September 1966, undated (Box 3)
  - Marshall, Carey, 28 March 1946 (Box 3)
  - Marshall, Georgina. (2), 11 May 1945 –10 February 1946 (Box 3)
  - Martin, Edward. (2), 12 January 1954 –13 January 1954 (Box 3)
  - Martin, Irene. (2), 4 September 1947 -22 November 1949 (Box 3)
  - Martzall, Marty, 13 October 1964 (Box 3)
  - Marx, Gerhard, 30 June 1966 (Box 3)
  - Mathais, James F. (13), 12 May 1953 –12 February 1964 (Box 3)
  - Mathis, William S. (3), 14 April 1971 –3 February 1972 (Box 3)
  - Mattiza, Joyce. [To Audrey Clark], 10 July 1947 (Box 3)
  - Mautner, Franz. (22), 7 January 1938 –24 June 1970 (Box 3)
  - Maxwell, Wood, 28 February 1947 (Box 3)
  - May, Charles E. (5), 15 November 1950 –1 December 1950, undated (Box 3)
  - Mayer, Elisabeth. (7), 14 November 1940 –22 November 1947 (Box 3)
  - Mayer-Kaupp. H. (3), 9 December 1960 -13 July 1965 (Box 3)
  - McBride, Julius, 14 July 1947 (Box 3)
  - McCaleb, Jean, 13 February 1947 (Box 3)
  - McCann, S. G, 6 July 1933 (Box 3)
  - McCants, J. T, 13 June 1932 (Box 3)
  - McCarthy, John A. (5), 12 February 1973 –14 September 1973 (Box 3)
  - McClain, William H. (5), 27 September 1958 –25 January 1972 (Box 3)
  - McCloskey, Carl T. Undated (Box 3)
  - McConnell, T. R. (2), 22 December 1947 –8 January 1948 (Box 3)
  - McCort, Dennis. (3), 12 April 1972 –13 May 1972, undated (Box 3)
  - McCready, Mac, 21 October 1946 (Box 3)
  - McDonald, William C. (2), 31 October 1972 –11 December 1972 (Box 3)
  - McFarland, J. Horace. (28), 14 May 1945 –17 September 1947 (Box 3)
  - McGary, Khadijah. (12), 14 February 1954 –19 March 1961, undated (Box 3)
  - McGaw, Robert A, 27 August 1963 (Box 3)
  - McGillicuddy, ? Undated (Box 3)
  - McGinnity, Dale, 13 December 1967 (Box 3)
  - McGovern, George. Undated (Box 3)
  - McGovern, Gordon, 12 August 1974 (Box 3)
  - McGregor, Helen. (10), 22 June 1926 –9 August 1937 (Box 3)
  - McKee, S. K. (2), 11 July 1952 –7 August 1952 (Box 3)
  - McKelvey, Christine, 6 November 1970 (Box 3)
  - McKillop, Alan D, 9 January 1948 (Box 3)
  - McKrause?, F. E, 25 November 1946 (Box 3)
  - McNabb, Eula M. Undated (Box 3)
  - McVey, William M. (2), 16 December 1957, undated (Box 3)
  - Meckel, Annemarie. (22), 27 November 1931 –22 November 1960, undated (Box 3)
  - Meckel, Eberhard. (11), 4 January 1949 -Christmas 1962, undated (Box 3)
  - Meesen, Hubert. J. (11), 10 February 1950 –27 March 1962, undated (Box 3)
  - Meesen, Lois, 26 May 1962 (Box 3)
  - von der Mehden, Fred R, 22 April 1970 (Box 3)
  - Meibrauch, Gisela, 28 March 1960 (Box 3)
  - Mellinder, George, 31 July 1930 (Box 3)
  - Mendel, Eva-Maria. Undated (Box 3)
  - Mendels, Judy. (3), 25 February 1956 –2 March 1956, undated (Box 3)
  - Mendenhall, Howard, 5 November 1946 (Box 3)
  - Menge, Karl. (3) Undated (Box 3)
  - Mercer, Sherwood R. (6), 20 November 1950 –21 November 1955, undated (Box 3)
  - Merkel, G. (18), 1 January 1940 –4 May 1960 (Box 3)
  - Merkenschlager, Hans. (3), 7 August 1949 -10 January 1966 (Box 3)
  - Merker, P. (4), 6 May 1927 -28 December 1927 (Box 3)
  - Merlander, Kurt. (4), 2 April 1948 –11 March 1952, undated (Box 3)
  - Merrett, Edgar P. (2), 18 September 1952 –25 May 1954 (Box 3)
  - Merrett, Eva, 24 September 1952 (Box 3)
  - Merrill, Vanita. (2), 26 May 1966 -3 November 1966 (Box 3)
  - Messinger, Grace and Bob. (13), 26 October 1961 –27 December 1972, undated (Box 3)
  - Messmer, Erich A, 19 January 1967 (Box 3)
  - Metcalf, George. (2), 10 May 1942 –11 November 1959 (Box 3)
  - Metcalf, K. D. (3), 24 October 1940 –30 November 1943 (Box 3)
  - Metzger, B. A, 25 September 1947 (Box 3)
  - Metzinger, ?, 21 March 1954 (Box 3)
  - Meyer, Mary Dinsmoor, 12 May 1943 (Box 3)
  - Meyer, G, 12 April 1961 (Box 3)
  - Meyer, Herman C, 9 March 1956 (Box 3)
  - Michael, Bess, 27 September 1966 (Box 3)
  - Michael, Friedrich. (3), 19 January 1951 –8 April 1953 (Box 3)
  - Michael, Wolfgang F, 7 December 1966 (Box 3)
  - Michalski, John. (2), 9 April 1971 –23 June 1971 (Box 3)
  - Michea, Rene. (41), 20 December 1932 –20 November 1967 (Box 3)
  - Midilrbon?, Christopher, 5 December 1966 (Box 3)
  - Milchi, Werner, 9 December 1949 (Box 3)
  - Miller, Robert A. (4), 18 October 1962 –9 May 1963 (Box 3)
  - Milstein, Barney M. (9), 6 March 1971 –28 January 1973 (Box 3)
  - Minor, Lucian W, 4 January 1966 (Box 3)
  - Mirus, Gerhard. (15), 10 October 1948 –30 September 1950, undated (Box 3)
  - Mitchell, Orva S. Undated (Box 3)
  - Mitchell, P. M, 22 March 1966 (Box 3)
  - Mittmeyer, ? (4), 21 December 1959 –13 March 1974 (Box 3)
  - Moblis. Christmas card, undated (Box 3)
  - Moe, Henry Allen. (20), 27 March 1953 –30 June 1963 (Box 3)
  - Moenkemeyer, Heinz, 18 January 1955 (Box 3)
  - Moet, Mary and Henry, 20 December 1960 (Box 3)
  - Mohn, Earl. (4), 20 October 1948 –5 January 1963 (Box 3)
  - Mohnhaupt, Curt, 13 March 1967 (Box 3)
  - Mohrdiek, Martin, June 1939 (Box 3)
  - de Mol, Willem Eduard. (5), 8 March 1950 –8 August 1953 (Box 3)
  - Moller, R. S, 8 July 1947 (Box 3)
  - Mommsen, Katharina and Momme. (31), 12 July 1959 –21 October 1972, undated (Box 3)
  - Mommsen, Wilhelm, 19 December 1949 (Box 3)
  - Monnig, Richard. (2), 4 February 1954 –19 October 1967 (Box 3)
  - Montealegre, Mariano R. (2), 15 December 1945 –22 July 1946 (Box 3)
  - Mook, Mildred K. Undated (Box 3)
  - Moore, Mrs. Edward Caldwell. Undated (Box 3)
  - Moore, Miriam, 26 March 1970 (Box 3)
  - Mordanle?, Dwight. Undated (Box 3)
  - Morelli, Anthony S, 28 January 1954 (Box 3)
  - Morgan, Arthur E, 2 April 1945 (Box 3)
  - Morgan, B. Q. (5), 10 December 1945 –17 March 1956 (Box 3)
  - Morgan, Bayard Quincy, December 1942 (Box 3)
  - Moriafustenwald?, (3) Christmas, 1969 –10 October 1971 (Box 3)
  - Morin, Richard W, 22 November 1944 (Box 3)
  - Möring, Guido. (30), 1 May 1957 –22 March 1971 (Box 3)
  - Morris, Raymond P, 9 July 1953 (Box 3)
  - Morrow, Glenn R, 24 October 1949 (Box 3)
  - Morrow, Marie Betzner, 10 February 1941 (Box 3)
  - Morton, Charles W, 6 November 1946 (Box 3)
  - Morton, Geoffrey B, 13 February 1953 (Box 3)
  - Motsch, Markus F. (4), 5 May 1972 –11 December 1972, undated (Box 3)
  - Moulton, William G. (2), 22 August 1952 –22 November 1970 (Box 3)
  - Moyer, P. W, 11 March 1949 (Box 3)
  - Mueller, Bertha. (2), 13 February 1954, undated (Box 3)
  - Mueller, Robert A, 10 May 1961 (Box 3)
  - von der Mühll, Peter. Undated (Box 3)
  - Müller, Allen. (11), 12 March 1963 –10 December 1964 (Box 3)
  - Müller, Gotthold, 22 April 1959 (Box 3)
  - Müller, Günther, 6 March 1960 (Box 3)
  - Müller, H. W, 19 May 1970 (Box 3)
  - Müller, Samuel F. (2), 19 July 1967 –31 July 1967 (Box 3)
  - Müller, ?, 14 December 1962 (Box 3)
  - Müller & Gräff. (3), 6 February 1952 –24 April 1959 (Box 3)
  - Mulloy, William J, 6 October 1949 (Box 3)
  - Münchner Verlag GMBH, 12 August 1948 (Box 3)
  - Munksgaard, Ejnar, 25 September 1953 (Box 3)
  - Muntyan, M, 7 November 1950 (Box 3)
  - Murphy, Fred P, 17 January 1945 (Box 3)
  - Murphy, Robert, December 1952 (Box 3)
  - Murray, Laura, 7 Agust 1962 (Box 3)
  - Murray, William L, 15 August 1955 (Box 3)
  - Muschg, Elli. (2), 1965, undated (Box 3)
  - Muschg, Walter. (2), 21 March 1949 –12 February 1956 (Box 3)
  - Myers, Walter, 3 February 1953 (Box 3)
- N
  - Nally, J. E, 29 March 1948 (Box 3)
  - Napasky, R. Undated (Box 3)
  - Nauberért, Christine. Undated (Box 3)
  - Naukler, Lamprothrym, 30 January 1942 (Box 3)
  - Naumann, Walter. (6), 15 February 1949 –19 May 1951, undated (Box 3)
  - Neitzel, ?, 12 August 1974 (Box 3)
  - Nellums, Mary. Christmas card, undated (Box 3)
  - Nelson, Elizabeth, 5 December 1966 (Box 3)
  - Nerreter, Paul. (8), 1939 –5 December 1967, undated (Box 3)
  - Neübraud, Elise. (2), 3 April 1958 –9 September 1959 (Box 3)
  - Neuer, Oscar. (6), 17 February 1949 –9 June 1950 (Box 3)
  - Neumann, Alfred R, 11 December 1952 (Box 3)
  - Neumann, Konrad, 19 July 1938 (Box 3)
  - Neunzig, Hans A, 3 October 1963 (Box 3)
  - Newald, Rinehard. (10), 31 October 1941 –3 April 1954 (Box 3)
  - Newmark, Maxim, 26 June 1954 (Box 3)
  - Nickson, Peggy White. (2), 1970, undated (Box 3)
  - van Niels, C. B, 17 June 1946 (Box 3)
  - Nienhuys, H. C, 4 December 1946 (Box 3)
  - Nietsch, ?, 24 October 1973 (Box 3)
  - Nijhoff, Martinus. (2), 23 November 1951 –18 May 1953 (Box 3)
  - Nixon, W. V, 25 May 1954 (Box 3)
  - Nolte, Fred O, 30 November 1949 (Box 3)
  - Norden, Heinz, 24 January 1954 (Box 3)
  - Nordmeyer, George. (13), 22 April 1942 –5 December 1955, undated (Box 3)
  - Nordmeyer, Heinrich. (67), 17 January 1941 –6 March 1974 (Box 3)
  - Norrenberg, Ursula. (6), 5 October 1951 –29 March 1955, undated (Box 3)
  - Nosthoff, Hans. (2), 22 December 1953 -23 May 1955 (Box 3)
  - Noth, Elena Fels. (7), 7 August 1955 –12 October 1955, undated (Box 3)
  - Noth, Ernst Erich. (92), 1 July 1942 –26 April 1963, undated (Box 3)
  - Novak, Richey. (5), 12 March 1970 –11 March 1971 (Box 3)
  - Novoportensis, Faber, May 1952 (Box 3)
  - Nuth, Leta, 4 December 1953 (Box 3)
  - Nye, Elizabeth. (3), 25 June 1931 –6 November 1931 (Box 3)
  - Nyland, W. A. (25), 13 February 1946 –14 August 1958 (Box 3)
- O
  - Oberle, Geo. D, 20 February 1946 (Box 3)
  - Ochs, F. (4), 22 November 1932 –26 December 1958 (Box 3)
  - Ogg, Frederic A, 22 May 1936 (Box 3)
  - Oliver, Medina, 21 February 1932 (Box 3)
  - Onest, Mark and Livy. (2) Christmas cards, undated (Box 3)
  - Oppenhiemer-?, Gabrielle and Paul. Christmas card, undated (Box 3)
  - O’Shea, Edward. Undated (Box 3)
  - Ouang, Tsin-Lon, 7 January 1939 (Box 3)
- P
  - P., Sandra. (10), 17 October 1971 –8 April 1973, undated (Box 3)
  - Paepcke, Ernst August. (3), 1 May 1938 –26 June 1939 (Box 3)
  - Paepcke, Walter P, 17 January 1950 (Box 3)
  - Paeschke, Hans. (6), 10 February 1949 –6 April 1950 (Box 3)
  - Palm, H. C, 20 February 1950 (Box 3)
  - Palmer, Lucille. Undated (Box 3)
  - Palmer, Martha E, 4 October 1966 (Box 3)
  - Palmer, P. M. (2), 31 January 1946 –13 December 1949 (Box 3)
  - Palmer?, F. (2), 23 June 1951 –29 November 1951 (Box 3)
  - Palo, Alice, 24 September 1943 (Box 3)
  - Papiroff, Herschel, 4 December 1945 (Box 3)
  - Parker, A. A, 8 January 1965 (Box 3)
  - Parker, William R. (10), 3 December 1947 –21 October 1954 (Box 3)
  - Parks, George B, 22 December 1953 (Box 3)
  - Parrish, Abraham, 3 January 1946 (Box 3)
  - Parthemore, P. M, 2 October 1945 (Box 3)
  - Parus Verlag, 13 July 1949 (Box 3)
  - Paschkis, Susanne and Victor. Christmas card, undated (Box 3)
  - Pattie, Mrs. F. A. [Billie], 11 April 1960 (Box 3)
  - Pattie, Franzl A. (300), 23 April 1943 –16 November 1973, undated (Box 3)
  - Paulsen, Hildegard. (20), 22 February 1947 –10 September 1955, undated (Box 3)
  - Paulsen, Wolfgang. (7), 26 January 1941 –19 November 1971 (Box 3)
  - Peabody, Brewster E, 26 February 1973 (Box 3)
  - Peacock, R. (6), 15 May 1951 –23 November 1973 (Box 3)
  - Peak, J. Hunter, 17 November 1965 (Box 3)
  - Pearce, Rex, 28 January 1946 (Box 3)
  - Pechel, Walburga, 17 December 1940 (Box 3)
  - Peech, Michael, 22 March 1946 (Box 3)
  - Pegoraro, Anna, 4 February 1971 (Box 3)
  - Peihker?, Annemarie, 10 September 1931 (Box 3)
  - Peisel, Herbert H. J, 22 October 1963 (Box 3)
  - Penn, Julia. (2), 16 November 1964, undated (Box 3)
  - Penney, R. D. (2), October 1940 –18 February 1942 (Box 3)
  - Pepper, Claude, 4 June 1940 (Box 3)
  - Perl, Walter H. (51), 2 March 1946 -7 May 1971, undated (Box 3)
  - Perlitz, Elsie, 30 October 1941 (Box 3)
  - Pessler, Wellmer, 30 October 1944 (Box 3)
  - Peters, W. W, 30 April 1951 (Box 3)
  - Peterson, Mr. and Mrs. Henry Martin, 1945 (Box 3)
  - Peuckert, Will-Erich. Undated (Box 3)
  - Peyre, Henri. M. (14), 4 January 1952 –22 November 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pfeffer, J. Alan. (5), 12 November 1948 –22 November 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pfeifer, Hoyt. (2) Undated (Box 3)
  - Pfeiffer, Ehrenfried. (8), 3 July 1945 –7 May 1947 (Box 3)
  - Pfeiler, William K. (5), 16 may 1942 –26 December 1958 (Box 3)
  - Pfleiger, Lloyd. (2), 12 November 1947, undated (Box 3)
  - Pflueger, Luther. (3), 15 June 1958, undated (Box 3)
  - Pfund, Harry. (4), 16 April 1939 –10 March 1968 (Box 3)
  - Pfund, Marie. (9), 2 April 1950 -22 December 1966, undated (Box 3)
  - Pfund, Marie and Harry. (7), 17 August 1950 –December 1971, undated (Box 3)
  - Pfund, Paul (2), 11 June 1946 –14 August 1947 (Box 3)
  - Phillips, Elias H. (2), 8 February 1957 –12 May 1959 (Box 3)
  - Phillipson, Ernst Alfred. (5), 2 November 1965 –30 March 1971 (Box 3)
  - Pichois, Claude. (19), 8 December 1970 –5 April 1974, undated (Box 3)
  - Pickett, Terry. (24), 4 December 1969 –12 December 1973, undated (Box 3)
  - Pilcher, Barbour Howe. (3), 12 September 1963 –12 December 1963 (Box 3)
  - Pinkus, A, 28 September 1953 (Box 3)
  - Pippincott, Peter. Undated (Box 3)
  - Pitcher, Eleanor, 29 January 1954 (Box 3)
  - Pivnicki, D. (2), 4 April 1964 –25 May 1964 (Box 3)
  - Planitz, Karl-Heinz. (5), 14 January 1941 –24 March 1956 (Box 3)
  - Plett, Emmi, 27 June 1969 (Box 3)
  - Poay, Jim and Jul. Christmas card, undated (Box 3)
  - Pohe, Stephen L. Undated (Box 3)
  - Polany, Michael, 31 December 1958 (Box 3)
  - Politzer, Heinz. (9), 20 April 1950 –14 August 1974 (Box 3)
  - Poore, Janet E, 2 September 1959 (Box 3)
  - Popple, Paul M, 27 September 1966 (Box 3)
  - Porter, Brigitte, 10 January 1971 (Box 3)
  - Porter, Olive, 12 December 1971 (Box 3)
  - Porter, Richard N, 4 November 1972 (Box 3)
  - Possenhofen, Harder, 16 October 1949 (Box 3)
  - Poteet, Kathryn, 17 November 1944 (Box 3)
  - Potter, D. Roland, 4 May 1944 (Box 3)
  - Potter, David M, 11 July 1950 (Box 3)
  - Potter, Frederico. Undated (Box 3)
  - Potts, Amadeus. Undated (Box 3)
  - Potts, Bishop, 25 November 1947 (Box 3)
  - Potts, M. Winifred, 20 December 1943 (Box 3)
  - Powell, Fred. (2), 4 May 1960 –8 May 1960 (Box 3)
  - Powell, ? Undated (Box 3)
  - Preller, H, 12 April 1967 (Box 3)
  - Prescott, Orville, 27 April 1950 (Box 3)
  - Preston, ?, 12 September 1953 (Box 3)
  - Pretzel, Ulrich. (13), 21 April 1967 –27/28 April 1974 (Box 3)
  - Price, Alfred W, 14 November 1971 (Box 3)
  - Price, Blanche A. (2), 29 November 1964 –1 January 1965 (Box 3)
  - Price, Lawrence M. (5), 21 February 1950 –7 March 1955, undated (Box 3)
  - Priebe, Mr. and Mrs. Ernst Bernard, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Priest, George M. (7), 15 May 1939 –28 January 1942 (Box 3)
  - Primo, Grace. [To Miss Clark], 3 December 1945 (Box 3)
  - Pringle, John P. (2), 9 November 1944 –29 November 1944 (Box 3)
  - Proctor, J. Undated [Sketch] (Box 3)
  - Proctor, Virginia, 6 July 1953 (Box 3)
  - Pröll, F. X, 1 December 1967 (Box 3)
  - Pryor, William C. (4), 9 May 1945 –30 April 1947 (Box 3)
  - Pulver, Johannes, 29 December 1952 (Box 3)
  - Purdie, Nan. Undated (Box 3)
  - Purdy, R. R. (2), 7 May 1967 –17 August 1971 (Box 3)
  - Purin, Charles M, 1 June 1951 (Box 3)
  - Pusey, Nathan M. (5), 30 November 1949 -14 October 1955 (Box 3)
  - Putzel, Max J. (18), 17 July 1969 –12 February 1973 (Box 3)
  - Pyritz, Hans, 1 January 1953 (Box 3)
- R
  - Raaf, Frieda. (2), 20 September 1932 -11 September 1933 (Box 4)
  - von Radecki, Sigismund, 23 December 1966 (Box 4)
  - Randall, David A, 21 October 1958 (Box 4)
  - Ransom, H. H. (4), 19 May 1960 –26 January 1961, undated (Box 4)
  - Rauscher, Gerhard. (2), 26 October 1970 –15 December 1970 (Box 4)
  - Ray, Gordon N. (5), 22 November 1960 –2 April 1974 (Box 4)
  - Read, Benjamin H. (2), 5 November 1973 –13 November 1973 (Box 4)
  - Reading H. E, 7 March 1958 (Box 4)
  - Reder, Ernst, 30 October 1961 (Box 4)
  - Reed, Lillian, 15 January 1941 (Box 4)
  - Rees, Edward H, 23 January 1953 (Box 4)
  - Reger, Max, 7 November 1914 (Box 4)